Register to The Charles Ives Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, Series III; 13 boxes
  - Correspondence - General, III.A
    - Parmelee, Lucy C., 1925 Dec 29; autograph postcard signed (Box 31, Folder 2)
      See also III.B/35/4/New Friends Mus
    - Pazmor, Radiana, 1933 Jul 29; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives, [1933 Jul 29]; draft (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Pazmor, 1933 Aug 3, Aug 10, 1933 Sep 12, Sep 20, 1933 Sep 27; 5 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Edith Ives to Pazmor, 1933 Dec 3; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Pazmor, 1934 Nov 9; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives, 1934 Nov 13; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Pazmor, 1934 Dec 1; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives, [?1934]; draft (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Edith Ives for below, draft (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Edith Ives, 1937 Oct 14; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Pazmor, 1937 Oct 29, Jul [?]; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives for 1937 Nov 14, draft (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - copy of above by Edith Ives, 1937 Nov 14 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Pazmor, 1938 Mar 16; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1939 Jun 10; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives, 1939 Jun 10; draft (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Pazmor, 1939 Jun 27 (2); 2 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1939 Jul 7; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Pazmor, 1940 Mar 27; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Edith Ives, 1940 Mar 31; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Pazmor to Edith Ives, 1940 Apr 11; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Pazmor to Harmony Twichell Ives, 1940 Apr 21; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1940 Apr 25; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Pazmor, 1946 May 4; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1946 May 15; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Pazmor to Miller, Philip, [1960] Apr 14; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, no date; Christmas card (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Peirce, John W., 1933 Aug 22, Sep 6, 1934 Apr 10, 1935 Jan 23; 4 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Perez, Andres, 1948 Oct 14; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Perlis, Vivian
      III.A/27/12/Copland 1970 Mar 15
      III.B/34/14/Joslin Clinic
    - Perry, Ralph Barton address Charles Ives (from scrapbook), no date; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Persichetti to Charles Ives, 1944 [??]; typed (copy)
      - Persichetti, Mrs. (Dorothea), 1944 Aug 17; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to above, 1944 Aug 17; draft (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Persichetti, Dorothea and Vincent 1944 Oct 24, autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Persichetti, 1944 Dec 8; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Perullo, Louis, 1932 May 22; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Phelps, William L.
      See folder 31/6
    - Pike, Alfred, 1943 Mar 23; typed letter signed
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Pike for typed letter signed, 1943 Apr 11; envelope (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Plum, Abram M. to Charles Ives, 1946 Jul 13; *typed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Pollain, Rene, 1920 Jun 10; autograph card (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Harmony Twichell Ives to Pollikoff, Max, no date; draft
      - signed Pollikoff, Max, 1950 Dec 20; Christmas card (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Pomphrey, Carolyn, no date; autograph card signed
        - Charles Ives to above, 1922 Dec 26; (copy) and letter (Box 31, Folder 4)
        - Pomphrey, 1923 Jan 5; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Pool, Morris W., 1922 Feb 10; autograph letter signed
      - Charles Ives to above, 1922 Feb 14; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to New York Herald Tribune re above, 1922 Feb 14; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Pool, 1922 Aug 8; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Poverty, Flat (Gavin, Michael), 1947 May 15; typed letter signed
      - (Lewis, George A.), 1931 Jan 11, 1935 Nov 21, 1936 Mar 21; 3 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Lewis, George A., 1933 Oct 27; typed letter signed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Proctor, Leland, 1945 Mar 12; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Proctor, Minnie, 1941 Jul 27; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Prostakoff, Josef, 1932 Dec 5; autograph letter signed
      - Prostakoff, 1933 Feb 17; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Edith Ives for Charles Ives to above, autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Prout, Louis B., 1921 Mar 19; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Putnam, F.B., 1939 Aug 3, 1940 Aug 31; 2 typed letters signed
      - Putnam, 1940 Oct 14; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Pynn, Norris Alan, 1949 May 4; autograph letter signed
      - Harmony Twichell Ives to above, draft (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Pynn, 1949 May 26; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Pynn to Harmony Twichell Ives, 1963 Jul 11; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Phelps, William Lyon (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Phelps, 1920 Jun 17; autograph letter signed and typed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Phelps, 1920 Jul 4; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives, 1920 Dec 21; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Phelps, William Lyon, (copy) of above, signed (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Phelps, 1920 Dec 26; autograph letter signed and typed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives, 1921 Dec 5; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Phelps, 1921 Dec 7; typed letter signed and typed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Phelps, 1923 Apr [2]; autograph letter signed and typed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives to above with corrections, 1937 Jan 4; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - 1937 Jan 4, Jan 6, 3 drafts (corrected) of above (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - letter sent Charles Ives, 1937 Jan 11; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Phelps, 1939 Feb 27; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Phelps, 1939 May 26; autograph letter signed and typed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Phelps autobiography, 1939 May 26; review and copy (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Yale Alumni Magazine with photo, 1941 May 9; cover (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Phelps, 1943 Aug 23; 3 obituaries (copies) (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Phelps, William Lyon, 2 printed announcements of Phelps Memorial (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Randall, Wm. W., 1922 Aug 31; autograph memo signed (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Charles Ives to Randall, 1922 Aug 31; draft (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Randall, 1922 Oct 9; autograph memo signed (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Reis, Claire
      III.B/34/13/ISCM
      III.B/34/14/League
    - Remaily, George to Harmony Twichell Ives & Charles Ives, 1946 May 10; *typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Reynolds, Vicki
      See 31/15/Schmitz 1945 Dec 26
    - Riegger, Wallingford
      See folder 31/13
    - Riehle, Evelyn, [?] Feb 17; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Ritchey, Hazel E., 1923 May 19; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Charles Ives to Ritchey, 1923 Jun 6; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Robb, J.D., 1951 Mar 8; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Robbins, Howard C., hymn book signed (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Roberts, George and family (Box 31, Folder 8)
      (all copies transcribed and typed by John Kirkpatrick unless noted)
      - Charles Ives to Roberts, 1934 May 12, Jun 15, 1934 Jul 22, 1935 [?] Jun, 1935 Jun 24; 5 items (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Charles Ives to Roberts, 1935 Jun 20; autograph letter signed (copy) with envelope (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Charles Ives, 1935 Jun [?], 1935 Jun [?], 1935 Jul, 1935 Jul 19; 4 items (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Charles Ives, 1935 Jul 31; autograph letter signed (copy) with envelope (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Charles Ives, 1935 Aug 2, Aug 4, 1935 Aug 20, Oct 15, 1936 Jun 18, Jul 29, 1940 Nov 21; 6 items (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Charles Ives transcribed by John Kirkpatrick, 1940 Nov 21; draft (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Roberts, Janet, 1942 Jan 18; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Roberts, Mrs. Eleanor, 1942 Jan [?]; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Charles Ives, no date; 2 drafts (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1942 Oct 19; 2 drafts with envelope (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - transcribed by John Kirkpatrick, 1942 Oct 19 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Roberts, George transcribed by John Kirkpatrick, [? 1942 Fall]; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - George and Eleanor, 1946 May 17; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - George and Eleanor, Christmas card (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Roberts, Eleanor to John Kirkpatrick, 1978 Feb 3; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Roberts [?], Janet, no date; Christmas cards (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Rodriguez, Jose, [?] Mar 20; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Charles Ives to Rodriguez, no date; 2 drafts (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Rogal-Lewitzsky
      See 28/9/Cowell 1934 Jun 9
    - Rogers, C.
      See 28/9/Cowell 1934 Nov 26, 1935 Mar [?]
    - Roldan, Amadeo, 1931 Aug 27; typed letter (copy)
      - Roldan, 1931 Aug 27; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Roldan, 1931 Oct 1, Dec 23; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Romm, Charles, 1923 Jun 4; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Charles Ives to Romm, 1923 Jun 6; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Roosevelt, President
      See II.B/25/8/Political writings
    - Rosborough, John W., 1922 Oct 21 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Charles Ives to Rosborough, 1922 Oct 30; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Charles Ives to Rosenfeld, Paul, no date; 2 drafts
      - Rosenfeld, 1940 Mar 26; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Charles Ives to above, 2 drafts (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Charles Ives re Rosenfeld, no date; 2 drafts (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Mellquist, Jerome, 1948 Apr 23; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Charles Ives to Ross, Stuart, 1917 Apr 11, May 3; 2 typed letters (copy) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Ross, Victor K.D., 1947 Sep 16; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Ross, Victor K.D., 1947 Sep 16; copy of above, signed (enc copy letter agreement) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Rothe, Friede F. for Arrau, Claudio, 1947 Sep 10; typed letter signed
      - Charles Ives to above, 1947 Oct 10; draft (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Rothe, 1951 Jun 22; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 9)
        enc questionnaire
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Roussel, Albert, 1922 Aug 20; autograph card signed with envelope (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Roussel, [?] Mar 20; autograph calling card (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Tickets for concert of Rovinsky, Anton (enc program list and publishers list), 1942 Feb 8; typed list
      - Rovinsky, 1930 Apr 30, Aug 21; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Roy, Leo, 1951 Mar 6; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Rudhyar, Dane (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Rudhyar (enc flyer re publication), 1930 Jul 5; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Rudhyar, 1938 Oct 21; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Rudhyar, [1939?] Aug 10; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Rudhyar, 1939 Aug 22; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Charles Ives reply to above, draft (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Charles Ives, 1939 Sep 7; cancelled check signed (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - (enc in memo from Rudhyar), 1939 Sep 11 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Rudhyar, 1939 Sep 11, 1940 Jan 2; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Charles Ives to above, 1939 Sep 11; draft (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Rudhyar, 1940 Mar 11, [19?] Oct 14; 2 typed letters signed (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Rudhyar, 1940 Nov 3, [?] Oct 31, 1949 Apr 2, envelope for [?] Dec 13; 4 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Rudhyar, D., [?] Jan 27; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - ("Seed Ideas") Rudhyar, D.; editor with Charles Ives marginalia, announcement (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Charles Ives to Rudhyar, no date; *draft (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Ruff, Erwin, 1942 Mar 24; *typed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Ruggles, Carl
      See folders 31/11 31/12
    - Russell, G.C. with marginalia Charles Ives, 1922 Nov 1; autograph memo
      - Charles Ives to above, 1922 Dec 12; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - to Russell, [?], no date; draft (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Ryders, no date; autograph card signed (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Ruggles, Carl (Box 31, Folder 11)
      Tentative list by John Kirkpatrick (5 pages)
      Carl Ruggles Papers, Yale Music Library
      - Mus. Am., 1932 Jan 23; article (copy) (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - John Kirkpatrick to Charles Ives, [?1932 Feb 26]; telegram (copy) (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Ruggles, [1932 Mar 2]; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives, [?1932 Nov 20]; draft autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Schmitz, verso to same (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives, [? 1932 Nov 20]; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives by John Kirkpatrick, [? 1932 Nov 20]; (copies) (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Ruggles, 1933 Aug 17; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Ruggles, 1934 Apr 30, Aug 8; 2 autograph cards (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Ruggles, 1934 Dec 15; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives, [1935 Oct 5); letter (copy by John Kirkpatrick) (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Ruggles, Charlotte, 1935 Oct 8; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives to Charlotte, 1936 Jul 3; 2 copies (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - typed by John Kirkpatrick, 1936 Jul 12 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Ruggles, 1935 Oct 8; envelope (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - re Benton's Ruggles - transcription by John Kirkpatrick, [? 1937 Fall]; news clippings (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives transcription by John Kirkpatrick, [? 1937 Fall]; draft (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Ruggles, Charlotte, 1938 Mar, 1938 Apr; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Ruggles, 1938 Apr 18; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives, [?1938 May 9]; (copy) (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - John Kirkpatrick, 1938 Mar 9; (copy) (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - transcription by John Kirkpatrick, 1938 Dec; autograph card signed (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Ruggles, 1939 Sep 8; autograph letter signed, envelope (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives, 1939 Sep 12; typed (John Kirkpatrick copy) (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Ruggles with music "Angels", 1939 Sep 21; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Ruggles, 1939 Oct 7; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives transcription by John Kirkpatrick, 1940 or 1941 [?]; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - 1940 Dec 22, autograph card (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives, 1941 Jan 6; John Kirkpatrick (copy) (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Ruggles [with music], 1941 Feb 1, 1941 Dec 22; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - 1943 Dec 18, card and envelope (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Harmony to Charlotte, 1944 Mar 16; John Kirkpatrick (copy) (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - (with music), 1944 Mar 21; autograph letter signed, envelope (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Harmony to Ruggles, 1944 Apr 2; John Kirkpatrick (copy) (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Ruggles, 1944 Aug 11; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Evocation No. 4 with dedication autograph, 1944 Aug 11; photostat (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Charles Ives, 1944 Aug 21; draft (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - transcription by John Kirkpatrick (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 1944 Dec, Christmas card (with music) (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 1945 Dec, envelope (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 1945 Dec, Christmas card (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Ruggles, 1947 May 21; autograph letter signed with envelope (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Charles Ives to above, 2 drafts (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 1948 Mar 18, program (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 1949 Dec, Christmas card (with music) (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - envelope and, 1950 Mar 20; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Ruggles, 1950 May 19; autograph card (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - John Kirkpatrick of Charles Ives, 1950 May 19; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Ruggles and envelope, 1950 Nov 10; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - transcription by John Kirkpatrick (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - John Kirkpatrick of Charles Ives, 1950 Nov 15; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Ruggles, 1950 Dec; Christmas card (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 1951 Feb 13, clipping (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 1951 Feb 14, card (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 1951 Feb 14, envelope (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1951 Apr 16; typed letter (copy) John Kirkpatrick (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1951 Sep 16; autograph letter (copy) John Kirkpatrick (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Charles Ives for National Institute of Arts and Letters recommendation for, 1952 Sep 29; draft (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - transcription by John Kirkpatrick (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - typed letter of above by Charles Ives, 1952 Sep 29 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 1952 Sep 29, (copy) signed of above (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1953 Mar 24, Sep 21; 2 copies by John Kirkpatrick (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Ruggles, 1954 Feb 8; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Ruggles, 1954 Mar 20; telegram (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Ruggles, 1954 Jun 22; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - John Kirkpatrick of Harmony Twichell Ives, 1954 Jun 13, 1954 July, 1955 Aug 25; 3 typed letters (copy) (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1958 Jul 15; letter (copy by John Kirkpatrick) (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Ruggles sketch to Boldt, [?] re Charles Ives, [1959 Oct 9]; letter (copy by John Kirkpatrick) (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Ruggles to Boldt, 1959 Oct 9; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Riegger, Wallingford (Box 31, Folder 13)
      III.A/28/2/Cowell
      III.B/24/9/Pan American Assn
    - Riegger, 1932 Feb 28; typed letter signed
      - 1932 May 4, autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Riegger, 1932 Feb 28; typed letter (copy) of above (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - 1933 May 10, Dec 14, 2 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Charles Ives response to 1934 May, no date; 2 drafts (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Riegger, 1934 May 16, May 24; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Charles Ives response to 1934 May 24, no date; draft (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Riegger, 1934 May 29, Sep 14, 1937 Jun 12, Aug 4; 4 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Charles Ives response to 1937 Aug 4, no date; draft (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Riegger, 1938 Jun 11, Nov 27, 1939 Jan 18, Feb 20, 1939 Oct 27; 5 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Riegger, 1946 Mar 6, 1947 May 8; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Riegger, 1948 Feb 29; program (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - 1948 Feb 24, Mar 7, 2 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Charles Ives response to 1948 Mar 7, no date; draft (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Riegger, 1949 Jan 6, Feb 18; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Saenger, Oscar, 1923 Apr 19; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Sagvl, Edith, 1950 Jan 2, 1951 Mar 15; 2 typed letters signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Sajous, Louis, 1923 May 6; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Salzedo, Carlos, no date; typed letter signed
      - Salzedo, 1932 Apr 13; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - excerpt Salzedo, 1934 May 4; typed (copy) (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Salzedo with marginalia Charles Ives, 1937 Mar 16; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Samaroff, Olga, 1922 Aug 9; typed letter (Box 31, Folder 14)
      See also III.B/34/13/ISCM
    - Sanford, Gertrude, 1942 Mar 9, 1949 Apr 3; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Sanjuan, Pedro, 2 envelope
      - Sanjuan, 1931 Aug 5; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Sanjuan, 1932 Jan 5; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Sanjuan, 1932 Feb 15, Jun 15, 1932 Aug 9, 1941 Mar 8, 1941 [??]; 5 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - St. Edmonds, H.
      See 28/9/Cowell 1932 Sep 22
    - St. Jaksic, 1951 Sep 8; typed letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Santvoord, G.
      See 29/1/Donovan 1953
    - Satcher, Herbert, 1922 Aug 25; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Saum, Leo, 1922 Aug 4; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Saunders, George, 1922 Aug 17; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Sawyer, Wilson, 1946 May 26; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Schaefer, Eugenia Ives, 1946 Oct 22, no date, no date; 3 autograph letters signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Schechtman, Saul, 1949 Feb 26; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Schecter, Ralph (Dickinson College) 1944 Jan 13, typed letter signed
      - from Edith Ives to above with scribbles, 2 envelopes (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Schecter, Ralph, 1944 Jan 25, Mar 30; 2 typed letters signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Schellman [?], Mrs. H.A., 1922 Aug; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Schieffelin, Mary Schuyler to Edith Ives, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Schirmer, E.C.
      See III.B/35/11/Schirmer
    - Schmitz, E. Robert (Box 31, Folder 15)
      See 31/11/Ruggles verso of [? 1932 Nov 20]
      III.B/35/9/Pro-Musica Society
      II.A/24/12/Quarter-tone article
      John Kirkpatrick listing of Schmitz correspondence 2 pp.
      E. Robert Schmitz Papers, Yale Music Library
      - Schmitz, Robert, 1923 Oct 4; autograph letter signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Charles Ives, [?1923] Oct 8; 2 drafts (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - transcription by John Kirkpatrick, 1923 Dec 9 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Charles Ives, 1923 Dec 9; typed draft and (copy) (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - New York Times, 1924 Oct 22; advertisement (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Charles Ives, 1925 Jul 30; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Schmitz, 1925 Sep 3, Mar 15, 1925 Nov 20, Jul 5; 4 typed letters signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Schmitz to Mason, Henry, 1926 Mar 19; (copy) (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Schmitz, 1926 Apr 5, Jul 28; 2 typed letters signed (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Schmitz, 1926 Dec 2; typed letter (copy) (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Schmitz, 1927 May 19; autograph card (Box 31, Folder 14)